<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brennan Macaig</title><link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/</link><description>Recent content on Brennan Macaig</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 12:07:32 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brennanmacaig.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hi, I'm Brennan.</title><link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 12:09:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/about/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Site Reliability Engineering Intern at DraftKings and a FIRST robotics mentor. I&amp;rsquo;m currently based out of Lowell MA (greater Boston area).
As a site reliability engineer, I focus on building secure, scalable, maintainable infrastructure - leveraging tools like terraform and DNSControl to achieve these goals. Previously, I worked as a full stack web developer, writing performance-oriented business-to-business SaaS apps.
In my free time, I maintain a blog, as well as develop personal IoT projects around the house.</description></item><item><title>Looking to reach me?</title><link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 12:09:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/contact/</guid><description>You can always email me at my personal email: me@brennanmacaig.com (I check this daily).
You could also @ me on my Twitter, or message me on my GitHub.
Further, you could try reaching me on LinkedIn, although I don&amp;rsquo;t check it very often.
I think you copied my content without permission I certainly hope not! If this is the case, please reach out to me immediately, and I&amp;rsquo;ll happily resolve the issue.</description></item><item><title>Howdy!</title><link>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 12:07:32 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.brennanmacaig.com/posts/welcome/</guid><description>My name is Brennan, and welcome to my new blog.
I&amp;rsquo;m trying to be more active in writing a blog - this will be mostly useless musings, with maybe the occasional interesting story.
A lot of what I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing will be something along the lines of &amp;ldquo;today I learned&amp;rdquo; - as I am very much still a student (oh hey, thanks Blake for this fantastic idea).
Recently, a friend of mine Nate started a new blog, which really inspired me to get on the blog writing train.</description></item></channel></rss>